Guide to the Undergraduate Financial Aid Office, Yale University, Financial Aid Records for the Classes of 1935-2005
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Undergraduate Financial Aid Office, Yale University, financial aid records for the Classes of 1935-2005
1931-2005
RU 101
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1198.5
(606 boxes)
The records consist of student records and financial aid materials of the Yale University Undergraduate Financial Aid Office.
Yale University. Undergraduate Financial Aid Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 11-C (YRG 11-C), Financial aid records for Yale undergraduate students.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted to the office of origin only.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records and financial aid materials of the Yale University Undergraduate Financial Aid Office.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scholarships; Student aid; Student financial aid administration; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Undergraduate Financial Aid Office
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1984, 1980-1984; Accession 1989-A-088
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to the office of origin only.
  - A-Bac (Box 1)
  - Bac-Ben (Box 2)
  - Ben-Bol (Box 3)
  - Bon-But (Box 4)
  - Cab-Chi (Box 5)
  - Chis-Cob (Box 6)
  - Cor-Dav (Box 7)
  - Dav-Dun (Box 8)
  - Dun-Fei (Box 9)
  - Fel-Gaf (Box 10)
  - Gai-Gol (Box 11)
  - Gal-Hal (Box 12)
  - Hal-Han (Box 13)
  - Hor-Jac (Box 14)
  - Jae-Kau (Box 15)
  - Kau-Kum (Box 16)
  - Kyl-Lip (Box 17)
  - Lit-Mac (Box 18)
  - Mad-Mar (Box 19)
  - Mas-Min (Box 20)
  - Mis-Mur (Box 21)
  - Mur-Orv (Box 22)
  - Osm-Pes (Box 23)
  - Pet-Ran (Box 24)
  - Rap-Ros (Box 25)
  - Ros-Sam (Box 26)
  - Sam-Sha (Box 27)
  - Sha-Smi (Box 28)
  - Smi-Sol (Box 29)
  - Sum-Tho (Box 30)
  - Tho-Ven (Box 31)
  - Ven-Wat (Box 32)
  - Wat-Wol (Box 33)
  - Wol-Z (Box 34)
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1985, 1981-1985; Accession 1990-A-094
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1986, 1982-1986; Accession 1991-A-096
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1987, 1983-1987; Accession 1992-A-053
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1988, 1984-1988; Accession 1993-A-046
  - A-Ask, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
  - As-Be, 1984-1988 (Box 2)
  - Ber-Bre, 1984-1988 (Box 3)
  - Bri-Bur, 1984-1988 (Box 4)
  - Bur-Chi, 1984-1988 (Box 5)
  - Chi-Cou, 1984-1988 (Box 6)
  - Cox-Dob, 1984-1988 (Box 7)
  - Dod-Eps, 1984-1988 (Box 8)
  - Ere-Fle, 1984-1988 (Box 9)
  - Fol-Gan, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
  - Ger-Gre, 1984-1988 (Box 11)
  - Gri-Har, 1984-1988 (Box 12)
  - Hes-Hog, 1984-1988 (Box 13)
  - Hol-Ise, 1984-1988 (Box 14)
  - Jac-Kee, 1984-1988 (Box 15)
  - Kef-Kub, 1984-1988 (Box 16)
  - Kul-Les, 1984-1988 (Box 17)
  - Lev-Lun, 1984-1988 (Box 18)
  - Lyn-Mas, 1984-1988 (Box 19)
  - Mau-Mih, 1984-1988 (Box 20)
  - Mil-Mor, 1984-1988 (Box 21)
  - Mos-Ned, 1984-1988 (Box 22)
  - Nel-Par, 1984-1988 (Box 23)
  - Pat-Pit, 1984-1988 (Box 24)
  - Ple-Ret, 1984-1988 (Box 25)
  - Reu-Rus, 1984-1988 (Box 26)
  - Rut-She, 1984-1988 (Box 27)
  - Shi-Spi, 1984-1988 (Box 28)
  - Spo-Tap, 1984-1988 (Box 29)
  - Tar-Van, 1984-1988 (Box 30)
  - Var-Wee, 1984-1988 (Box 31)
  - Weh-Won, 1984-1988 (Box 32)
  - Woo-Zus, 1984-1988 (Box 33)
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1989, 1985-1989; Accession 1994-A-107
  - A-Arm (Box 1)
  - Arn-Ben (Box 2)
  - Ben-Bro (Box 3)
  - Bro-Car (Box 4)
  - Car-Che (Box 5)
  - Chi-Con (Box 6)
  - Coo-Dek (Box 7)
  - Del-Egu (Box 8)
  - Ehr-Fla (Box 9)
  - Fle-Geo (Box 10)
  - Geo-Han (Box 11)
  - Han-His (Box 12)
  - Hob-Iwa (Box 13)
  - Jac-Kar (Box 14)
  - Kat-Kna (Box 15)
  - Koc-Lee (Box 16)
  - Lee-Loc (Box 17)
  - Lop-Mat (Box 18)
  - Mat-Mey (Box 19)
  - Mez-Mur (Box 20)
  - Mur-Oya (Box 21)
  - Uninventoried (Box 21A, Box 22–27)
  - Wag-Wil (Box 28)
  - Wil-Wu (Box 29)
  - Wu-Zwe (Box 30)
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1990, 1986-1990; Accession 1995-A-034
  Scope and Contents
  Boxes 1-12 missing.
  - A - AND, 1986-1990 (Box 1)
  - ANT - BAR, 1986-1990 (Box 2)
  - BAR - BIL, 1986-1990 (Box 3)
  - BIR - BRE, 1986-1990 (Box 4)
  - BRE - CAM, 1986-1990 (Box 5)
  - CAN-CHA, 1986-1990 (Box 6)
  - CHA-COH, 1986-1990 (Box 7)
  - COH - DAV, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
  - DAV-DOL, 1986-1990 (Box 9)
  - DON-ELI, 1986-1990 (Box 10)
  - ELL - FIG, 1986-1990 (Box 11)
  - FIN - GAR, 1986-1990 (Box 12)
  - GAV - GRA, 1986-1990 (Box 13)
  - GRE - HAS, 1986-1990 (Box 14)
  - HAV - HOL, 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - HOM - JON, 1986-1990 (Box 16)
  - JOR - KIL, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
  - KIM-KRY, 1986-1990 (Box 18)
  - KRO - LAT, 1986-1990 (Box 19)
  - LAU - LIN, 1986-1990 (Box 20)
  - LIN - LUM, 1986-1990 (Box 21)
  - LUN - MEE, 1986-1990 (Box 22)
  - MEH - MON, 1986-1990 (Box 23)
  - MON - NEE, 1986-1990 (Box 24)
  - NEL - OBO, 1986-1990 (Box 25)
  - OBR - PEL, 1986-1990 (Box 26)
  - PEN - PRU, 1986-1990 (Box 27)
  - PRY - RIC, 1986-1990 (Box 28)
  - RID-SAE (Box 29)
  - SAF - SEA, 1986-1990 (Box 30)
  - SED - SMI, 1986-1990 (Box 31)
  - SOK - TAN, 1986-1990 (Box 32)
  - TAN - TSO, 1986-1990 (Box 33)
  - TSO - WEB, 1986-1990 (Box 34)
  - WEC - WIL, 1986-1990 (Box 35)
  - WIN - ZOR, 1986-1990 (Box 36)
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1998, 1994-1998; Accession 2006-D-022
- Student financial aid files, Class of 1999, 1995-1999; Accession 2007-D-166
- Student financial aid files, Class of 2000, 1996-2000; Accession 2007-D-167
- Student financial aid files, Class of 2001, 1997-2001; Accession 2007-D-168
- Student financial aid files, Class of 2002, 1998-2002; Accession 2007-D-169
- Student financial aid files, Class of 2003, 1999-2003; Accession 2007-D-170
- Student financial aid files, Class of 2005, 2001-2005; Accession 2007-D-021